Leser, Paul; Papers ger058
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, associations, publishers, etc., 1920-1984; 6; 9 cubic ft. 496 file folders
  - Anthropos-Institut (Arnold Burgmann, P. Joseph Henninger, J. F. Thiel), Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 28)
    See also correspondence under Thiel.
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 29)
  - Antiquarians, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 30)
  - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Burg Waldeck, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 31)
  - Archeological Research Services, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 32)
  - Aschendorff Verlag, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 33)
  - Atlanta University, Georgia (Rushton Coulborn), 1949-1951 (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 34)
  - Atlas der Deutschen Volkskunde, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 35)
  - Aufbau (NY), Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 36)
  - Auswärtiges Amt, Berlin, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 37)
  - Berliner Gesellschaft für Anthropologie, Ethnologie und Urgeschichte, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 38)
  - Bernard Samter, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 39)
  - Besoldungskasse Hessen in Wiesbaden, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 40)
  - Beth Israel Congregation, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 41)
  - BJG International, Inc., Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 42)
  - Black Mountain College, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 43-44)
  - Blumenhaus Hugo und Max Jansen, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 45)
  - Board of Home Missions, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 46)
  - Bonner Turnverein, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 47)
  - Book orders, 1924-1926 (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 48)
  - Books & Cheese, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 49)
  - Boston University, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 50)
  - Bradley Field Enterprises / Air Travel Insurance Counter, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 51)
  - Brandeis University, Undated (Box 37 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 52)
  - Bratislava (Comenius University), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 1)
  - British Visa Office, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 2)
  - Brockhaus Enzyklopädie, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 3)
  - Buchladen Hans Linz, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 4)
  - Der Bücherwurm, Antiquariat, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 5)
  - Bund-Verlag GmbH, Köln, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 6)
  - Burian-Moss Photographers, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 7)
  - Burt Franklin Bookseller, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 8)
  - Canyon Records, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 9)
  - CARE, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 10)
  - Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, OH, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 11)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 12)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 13)
  - Chacmol, The Archeological Association of the University of Calgary, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 14)
  - Chaney, Ben (legal case), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 15)
  - Charlotte Child Study Club, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 16)
  - Charter Oak Community Church, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 17)
  - Chatsworth Florist, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 18)
  - Christian Science Monitor, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 19)
  - Christian Youth Corps, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 20)
  - CIBA Pharmaceutical Products, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 21)
  - The City Church (William J. Villaume), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 22)
  - Civitan Club, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 23)
  - Clark-Brewer Teachers' Agency, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 24)
  - Colby Hill Inn, Henniker, NH, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 25)
  - College Specialist Bureau, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 26)
  - Colloquium on Religious Presence, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 27)
  - Colonia-Versandbuchhandlung, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 28)
  - Committee for the Scientific Study of Religion, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 29)
  - Committee on International Exchange of Persons (Fulbright-Hays), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 30)
  - Concordia Seminary, St. Louis, MO, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 31)
  - Connecticut Association of Secondary Schools, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 32)
  - Connecticut Band and Trust Company, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 33)
  - Connecticut Blue Cross, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 34)
  - The Connecticut Conference of Social Work, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 35)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 36)
  - Connecticut Eye Bank, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 37)
  - Crusade for the Abolition of Cruelty, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 38)
  - Current Anthropology (Sol Tax, Ethel Nurge), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 39)
  - Current Anthropology -- "one" discussion, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 40)
  - Daniels Defense Committee, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 41)
  - Danish Ethnological Association / Dansk Etnografisk Forening, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 42)
  - Dauber & Pine Bookshops, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 43)
  - Deutsch-nordische Film-Union G.m.b.H., Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 44)
  - Deutsche Afrika-Gesellschaft e.V., Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 45)
  - Deutsche Bank, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 46)
  - Deutsche Bücherei, Leipzig, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 47)
  - Deutsche evangelisch-reformierte Gemeinde, Frankfurt a.M., Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 48)
  - Deutsche Gaue, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 49)
  - Deutsche Gesellschaft für Völkerkunde, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 50)
  - Deutsche Gesellschaft für Volkskunde e.V., Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 51)
  - Deutsche Verlags-Anstalt, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 52)
  - Deutsches Museum von Meisterwerken der Naturwissenschaft und Technik, München, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 53)
  - Dictionary of International Biography, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 54)
  - Directory of Social Sciences, Africa, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 55)
  - Dog Welfare Association of Connecticut, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 56)
  - Dokumentationszentrum des Bundes Jüdischer Verfolgter des Naziregimes, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 57)
  - Doubleday & Company, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 58)
  - E. I. Dupont de Nemours & Company, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 59)
  - E. Scheuer Books, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 60)
  - East European Quarterly (Stephen Fischer-Galati), Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 61)
  - Ebony, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 62)
  - Encyclopedia of Modern Christian Missions, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 63)
  - Encyclopedia of Religion, Undated (Box 38 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 64)
  - Epstein Travel Service, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 1)
  - The Erie Railway, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 2)
  - Ethnografski muzej, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 3)
  - Ethnologia Eurpaea (Günter Wiegelmann, G. de Rohan Csermak), Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 4)
  - Ethnologia Scandinavica, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 5)
  - Ethnological Atlas of Europe and its Bordering Countries, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 6)
  - Ethnologist's Book Exchange, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 7)
  - Eugen Diederichs Verlag, Jena, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 8)
  - Evangelische Kirchensteuer, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 9)
  - Exposition Press, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 10)
    See also Gertrud Wenzel.
  - Fachingen (mineral water), Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 11)
  - Fellowship of Professors of Missions, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 12)
  - Finanzamt, Frankfurt am Main, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 13)
  - Finnish National Commission for UNESCO, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 14)
  - First Congregational Church, Brimfield, MA (Reverend Robert D. Loggie), Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 15)
  - First Congregational Church, Olivet, MI, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 16)
  - Fleisch-Daum (Familie Reiffenstein), Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 17)
  - Folklore of Ireland Society, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 18)
  - Food parcels, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 19)
  - Fort Washington Collegiate Church, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 20)
  - Foster's Pen Shop, Olivet, MI, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 21)
  - Foto Wagner, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 22)
  - Frankfurter Anthropologische Gesellschaft, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 23)
  - Frankfurter Bücherstube, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 24)
  - Frankfurter Bund für Volksbildung, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 25)
  - Frankfurter General-Anzeiger, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 26)
  - Frankfurter Gesellschaft für Anthropologie, Ethnologie und Urgeschichte, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 27)
  - Frankfurter Nachrichten, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 28)
  - Frankfurter Sozietät-Druckerei, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 29)
  - Frankfurter Zeitung, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 30)
  - Frederick Ungar Publishing Co., Inc., Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 31)
  - Freies Bildungswerk Balduinstein e.V., Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 32)
  - Friedhofsgärtnerei Friedrich Müller, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 33)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 34)
  - Frobenius-Institut, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 35)
  - Fulbright Commission (Austrian-American Educational Commission), Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 36)
  - Furniture, Berlin, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 37)
  - G. & C. Merriam Company, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 38)
  - G.E.C. Gads Forlag, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 39)
  - German Consulate General, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 40)
  - Gesellschaft für den Volkskundeatlas in Österreich, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 41)
  - Gesellschaft für Erde- und Völkerkunde, Bonn, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 42)
  - Gesellschaft für Völkerkunde, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 43)
  - Gesellschaft für Völkerkunde, Mitteilungsblatt, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 44)
  - Gramercy Shipping Company, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 45)
  - Greater Hartford Community Council, Health Division, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 46)
  - Greece, Consulate General, Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 47)
  - Greyvan Lines, Inc., Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 48)
  - Gustav Wyneken-Gesellschaft, Göttingen e.V., Undated (Box 39 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 49)
  - H. Delliehausen (Spedition), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 1)
  - H. G. Ollendorff, Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 2)
  - H. L. Bronner's Druckerei, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 3)
  - Hambros Bank Limited, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 4)
  - Hartford Anthropological Society/Association, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 5)
  - Hartford Churches, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 6)
  - Hartford Consumers' Cooperative Association, Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 7)
  - The Hartford Courant, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 8)
  - Hartford Despatch and Warehouse Co., Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 9)
  - Hartford Get-Together Club, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 10)
  - The Hartford Times, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 11)
  - Harvard University Press, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 12)
  - Hauptstaatsarchiv, Düsseldorf, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 13)
  - Hebrew Sheltering and Immigrant Aid Society, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 14)
  - Herbert Lang & Cie, Berne, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 15)
  - Heye Foundation, Museum of the American Indian, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 16)
  - Hillyer College, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 17)
  - Historisches Museum, Frankfurt a.M., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 18)
  - Holland-America Line, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 19)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 20)
  - Hospitalization, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 21)
  - Hudson Parcels, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 22)
  - Human Relations Area Files (HRAF) Press, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 23)
  - Hutchings Psychiatric Center, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 24)
  - Idaho Historical Society, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 25)
  - Ideal Book Store, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 26)
  - Imperial Wear, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 27)
  - Income Tax, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 28)
  - Independent Cultural Association, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 29)
  - Individual Learning Systems, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 30)
  - Institut für deutsche Volkskunde, Berlin (1955 meeting), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 31)
  - Institut für Völkerkunde, Wien, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 32)
  - Institute for Sex Research, Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 33)
  - Institute for the Development of Alternatives to the Incarceration of Children (Edward Daniels), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 34)
  - Institute of Ethnology, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 35)
  - Institute of Pastoral Care, Inc., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 36)
  - Institutet för folklivsforskning, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 37)
  - Insurance (Penrose), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 38)
  - International Association for European Ethnology and Folklore, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 39)
  - International Association for Mission Studies (IAMS), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 40)
  - International Biographical Archives and Dictionary of Central European Émigrés, 1933-1945 (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 41)
  - International Bookfinders, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 42)
  - The International Conference for Research of Plowing Implements, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 43)
  - International Conference on theoretical and practical problems of the ethnology of Europe, Stockholm, 1965 September 01-1965 September 02 (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 44)
  - International Congress, Elisabethville, Congo, 1961 (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 45)
  - International Congress of Africanists, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 46)
  - International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences (III, 1948; IV, 1952), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 47)
  - International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences (V, 1956), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 48)
  - International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences (VI, 1960; VII, 1964), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 49)
  - International Congress of Historical Sciences, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 50)
  - International Council for Philosophy and Humanistic Studies, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 51)
  - International Development Placement Association, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 52)
  - International Directory of Anthropologists, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 53)
  - International Institute of Differing Civilizations, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 54)
  - International Journal of African Historical Studies, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 55)
  - International Review of Missions, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 56)
  - International Scholars Directory, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 57)
  - International Secretariat for Research on the History of Agricultural Instruments (George Nellemann, Axel Steensberg), Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 58)
  - International Sociological Association, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 59)
  - International Union of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 60)
  - Interart -- Buchversand, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 61)
  - Investments, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 62)
  - Israeli Embassy, Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 63)
  - James Keiller & Son, Ltd., Undated (Box 40 (6-Series 6 - Correspondence with institutions, ), Folder 64)